<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeannie Hong</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jeannie Hong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cool things about python (Regex)</title>
      <link>/blog/cool-things-about-python-regex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/cool-things-about-python-regex/</guid>
      <description>RegexRegular expression, also called regex, is a sequence of charaters that matches other sequences with certain patterns. It is kind of like a fancy version of ctrl+f using python!
Let’s look at some examples of regex!
library(reticulate)import restring1=&amp;quot;We have to extract these numbers 12, 47, 48 The integers numbers are also interesting: 189 2036 314\&amp;#39;,\&amp;#39; is a separator, so please extract these numbers 125,789,1450 and also these 564,90456 We like to offer you 7890$ per month in order to complete this task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>0) IntroductionThe dataset that I have chosen for this project is the Fitness Trends dataset (25.csv), which was found on kaggle.com. It contains 7 variables (date, step_count, mood, calories_burned, hours_of_sleep, bool_of_active, weight_kg) and 96 observations. The dataset gives information about feeling active based on number of steps walked, mood, calories burned, hourse of sleep, and weight. I thought this dataset was interesting to look at since excersing is often used as a treatment for people who feel lethargic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>0) IntroductionThe two datasets that I have chosen for this project is the Global Suicide Data (MH_12) and World Happiness Report (X2015), which were both found on kaggle.com. The Global Suicide Data contains 6 variables (Country, Sex, 2015, 2010, 2005, 2000) and 549 observations. It gives you the age-adjusted suicide rate (per 100,000) in different countries based on year and sex. The World Happiness Report contains 12 variables (Country, Region, Happiness rank, Happiness score, Standard Error, Economy, Family, Health, Freedom, Trust, Generosity, Dystopia residual) and 158 observations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Projects   Hello! Check out some projects I have been working on:
   Project 1     Project 2   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Jeannie Hong  I am an undergraduate biology student at University of Texas at Austin. I am in the health science scholars honors program in the college of natural sciences. My research focuses on studying the effects of female endogenous hormone on relapse of drug use, with particular focus on activation of nucleus accumbens. I enjoy watching horror movies and musicals in my free time.  Link  Git Hub  Education The University of Texas at Austin, Austin, TX</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>